Guide to the Kiwanis Club of Houston records, 1919-2017 MS 619
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Awards, 182624
  - Bush Awards, 183669
    - Bush Award, 2006; 182635 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Bush Award, 2008-2009; 182637 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Bush Award Applications, 2002-2003; 182638 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bush Award Applications (1 of 2), 2004; 182639 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Bush Award Applications (2 of 2), 2004; 182640 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bush Award Applications, 2005; 182642 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Bush Award Applications, 2006; 182643 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Bush Award Recipients, 2002; 182644 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Bush Award Recipients, 2003; 182645 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Bush Award Recipients, 2004; 182646 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Bush Award Recipients, 2005; 182648 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Bush Award Recipients, 2006; 182649 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Bush Award Runners-Up, 2004; 182650 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Bush Award Runners-Up, 2005; 182653 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Bush Award Runners-Up, 2006; 182654 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Bush Award: Invitations Media, Correspondence, Misc., 2002-2004; 182655 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Bush Award: Invitations Media, Correspondence, Misc., 2005-2006; 182656 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Bush Award: Photographs, 2005; 182657 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - George Bush Sports Hero Award, VHS (1 of 4), 182658 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - George Bush Sports Hero Award, VHS (2 of 4), 182659 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - George Bush Sports Hero Award, VHS (3 of 4), 182660 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - George Bush Sports Hero Award, VHS (4 of 4), 182661 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - George Bush Sports Hero Award, Betacam- Edited Tape, 2003; 182662 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - George Bush Sports Hero Award, Betacam (1 of 2), 2004; 182663 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - George Bush Sports Hero Award, Betacam (2 of 2), 2004; 182665 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scouts of America awards, 183672
    - Boy Scouts of America: Plaque- Benefactor Member, 182666 (Box 22, Item 1)
    - Boy Scouts of America: Plaque- Guardian Member, 182667 (Box 22, Item 2)
    - Boy Scouts of America: Plaque- Sponsor Member, 182668 (Box 22, Item 3)
    - Boy Scouts of America: Glass Disc- Outstanding Community Service "Scouting for Food", 182669 (Box 22, Item 4)
    - Boy Scouts of America: Outstanding Achievement and Contribution to "Scouting for Food", 182670 (Box 22, Item 5)
    - Boy Scouts of America: In appreciation to the Kiwanis club of houston, operation scoutreach, 182673 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - George E. Hixson Fellows, 183673
    - George E. Hixson Fellow: Plaque- General Maurice Hirsch, 1995; 182674 (Box 24, Item 1)
    - George E. Hixson Fellow: Plaque- W. Buck Arnold, 1995; 182675 (Box 24, Item 2)
    - George E. Hixson Fellow: Plaque- Winifred Hirsch, 1996; 182676 (Box 24, Item 3)
    - George E. Hixson Fellow: Medal and Pin (3 sets), 182677 (Box 24, Item 4)
    - George E. Hixson Fellow Files (2), 182678 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Diamond Section awards, 183674
    - Kiwanis International: Diamond Section Multiple Service Award, 1980-1981; 182679 (Box 24, Item 6)
    - Kiwanis International: Diamond Section Single Service Award, 1980-1981; 182680 (Box 24, Item 7)
  - Texas Society for the Prevention of Blindness awards, 183675
    - Texas Society for the Prevention of Blindness: Plaque- Certificate of Merit, 182681 (Box 24, Item 8)
    - Texas Society for the Prevention of Blindness: plaque- Distinguished Service Award (1), 182682 (Box 24, Item 9)
    - Texas Society for the Prevention of Blindness: plaque- Distinguished Service Award (2), 182683 (Box 25, Item 1)
  - Houston Food Bank, 183676
    - Houston Food Bank- Certificate of Appreciation presented to Kiwanis Club of Houston, 182684 (Box 25, Item 2)
    - Houston Food Bank- Certificate of Appreciation presented to Kiwanis Club of Houston, 182685 (Box 25, Item 3)
    - Houston Food Bank- Certificate of Appreciation presented to HSPVA, 182686 (Box 25, Item 4)
  - Alamo Award- Kiwanis Club of Houston, 1979; 182687 (Box 25, Item 5)
  - Kiwanis- Blank Certificates and Award, 182688 (Box 25, Item 6)
  - Newspaper Day Award- Certificate to George Carmark, 182689 (Box 25, Item 7)
  - Legion of Honor, 183677
    - Legion of Honor File, 1949-2000; 182690 (Box 25, Item 8)
    - Legion of Honor- Certificate and Pin, Risher Randall, 182691 (Box 25, Item 9)
    - Legion of Honor Pin, 182692 (Box 25, Item 10)
  - USO Certificated award to Houston Kiwanis Club- Distinguished War Service, 182693 (Box 25, Item 11)
  - Bicentennial Commission- Certificate "in recognition of the Kiwanis Club of Houston", 182694 (Box 25, Item 12)
  - Kiwanis International- Certificate of Appreciation to Kiwanis International Europe, 182695 (Box 25, Item 13)
  - American Legion Presented to Richard P. Ganchan, 1976; 182696 (Box 25, Item 14)
  - Good Samaritans: Plaque and Poster- Good Samaritan Program, 182697 (Box 26, Item 1)
  - RideOn: Plaque- In Appreciation of your Generosity and Support, 182698 (Box 26, Item 2)
  - H.E.R.O Project: Plaque- Presented with Appreciation…, 1988-1989; 182699 (Box 26, Item 3)
  - American Trauma Society Harris Unit: Plaque- With Appreciation…, 182700 (Box 26, Item 4)
  - New Directions: Plaque- Award of Appreciation, 1978, 182701 (Box 26, Item 5)
  - Kiwanis International: Plaque- Kiwanis Club Houston- In Recognition…, 1984; 182702 (Box 26, Item 6)
  - Salvation Army Red Shield Youth Center: Plaque- In Appreciation for Faithful and Devoted Service, 182703 (Box 26, Item 7)
  - Howell Cocke Annual Tennis Tournament: Winners, 1981-2003; 182704 (Box 26, Item 8)
  - President's Golf Tournament, 1974, 1975; 182705 (Box 26, Item 9)
  - Annual Charity Golf Tournament Champions, 1995; 182706 (Box 26, Item 10)
  - Kiwanis Bowling League Winners Trophy, 1944-1945; 183808 (Box 64, Item 1)
  - World Service Medal, 182707 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Layman of the Year, 1991; 182708 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - International Executive of the Year, 183678
    - International Executive of the Year, 1986-1996; 182709 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - International Executive of the Year, 1997-2004; 182710 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - International Executive of the Year, 2005-2009; 182711 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Clergyman Appreciation Day, 182712 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Distinguished Kiwanis Club International Foundation Awards, 182713 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - International Foundation Hixson Fellowship, 182714 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Certificate of Appreciation Award to Kiwanis Foundation, American Red Cross through the Bernice De Yoe Wood Fund, 182716 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Robert P. Connelly Heroism Award, 182717 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Distinguished Lt. Governor Award, 182718 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sustaining Donor, 182719 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Awards and Certificates of Appreciation, 182720 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Award- Kan Festival Recognitions, 1990; 182721 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Award- 1st Place Outstanding Bulletin, 182722 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Recognitions of Superior and Quality Sponsorship, 182723 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Series VI: Conventions, 182724
  - Atlantic City, NJ 1949, 182725 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Convention Programs, 1952, 1955, 1962, 1963; 182726 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Chicago, IL, 1962; 182727 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Houston, TX. Convention, 1967; 182728 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Atlantic, Georgia Convention, 1975; 182729 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Phoenix, AZ, 1984; 182730 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Toronto, Ontario, 1985; 182731 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Houston, TX 1986, 182732 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Costa Rica, 1987; 182733 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Washington, D.C., 1987; 182735 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Seattle, WA, 1988; 182736 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Orlando, FL, 1989; 182737 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - St. Louis, MO, 1990; 182738 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Anaheim, CA, 1991; 182739 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Indianapolis, IN, 1992; 182740 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Galveston, TX, 1993; 182741 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Nice, France, 1993; 182742 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - New Orleans, LA, 1994; 182743 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Las Vegas, NV, 1995; 182744 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Salt Law City, UT, 1996; 182745 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Nashville, TN, 1997; 182746 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Montreal, Canada, 1998; 182747 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Miami Beach, FL, 2000; 182748 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - New Orleans, 2002; 182749 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - St. Louis, MO, 2004; 182750 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Honolulu, HI, 2005; 182751 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Montreal, Canada, 2006; 182752 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - San Antonio, TX, 2008; 182753 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Resolutions Adopted at Conventions, 182754 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Convention Correspondence, 182755 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - District Conventions: Delegates and Alternatives, 182756 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Waco, TX (District), 1973; 182757 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Oklahoma City, OK (District), 1974; 182758 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Brownsville, TX (District), 1975; 182759 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Galveston, TX (District), 1979; 182760 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Abilene, TX (District), 1981; 182761 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - McAllen, TX (District), 1982; 182762 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Waco, TX (District), 1983; 182763 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Austin, TX (District), 1984; 182764 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Corpus Christi, TX (District), 1985; 182765 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Tulsa, OK (District), 1986; 182766 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Beaumont, TX (District), 1987; 182767 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Lubbock, TX (District), 1988; 182768 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Wichita Falls, TX (District), 1989; 182769 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - College Station, TX (District), 1990; 182770 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Tyler TX (District), 1991; 182771 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Arlington, TX (District), 1992; 182772 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Galveston, TX (District), 1993; 182773 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - San Antonio, TX (District), 1996; 182774 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Conventions (District), 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - OK City, OK (District), 2004; 182775 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Cruise (District), 2006; 182776 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Convention Delegates and Alternates, 1972-1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Series VII: Bulletins, 182777
  - The Kiwanian, 1925; 182778 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The Builder, 1927-1928; 182779 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - The Builder, 1928-1929; 182780 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - The Kiwanian, 1929; 182781 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - The Kiwanian, 1930; 182782 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - The Kiwanian, 1931; 182783 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - The Kiwanian, 1932; 182784 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - The Kiwanian, 1933; 182785 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - The Kiwanian, 1934-1937; 182786 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - The Kiwanian, 1936-1938; 182787 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - The Kiwanian, 1941-1942; 182788 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - The Kiwanian, 1948; 182789 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - The Kiwanian, 1949; 182790 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - The Kiwanian, 1950; 182791 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - The Kiwanian, 1951; 182792 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - The Kiwanian, 1952; 182793 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - The Kiwanian, 1953; 182794 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - The Kiwanian, 1954; 182795 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - The Kiwanian, 1955; 182796 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - The Kiwanian, 1956; 182797 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - The Kiwanian, 1957; 182798 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - The Kiwanian, 1958; 182799 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - The Kiwanian, 1959; 182800 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - The Kiwanian, 1960; 182801 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - The Kiwanian, 1961; 182802 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Kiwanian, 1962; 182803 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - The Kiwanian, 1964; 182804 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - The Kiwanian, 1965; 182805 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Kiwanian, 1966; 182806 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - The Kiwanian, 1967; 182807 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Kiwanian, 1968; 182808 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - The Kiwanian, 1969; 182809 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - The Kiwanian, 1969-1970; 182810 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - The Kiwanian, 1970-1971; 182811 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - The Kiwanian, 1971-1972; 182812 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - The Kiwanian, 1972-1973; 182813 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - The Kiwanian, 1973-1974; 182814 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - The Kiwanian, 1974-1975; 182815 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - The Kiwanian, 1975-1976; 182816 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - The Kiwanian, 1976-1977; 182817 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - The Kiwanian, 1977-1978; 182818 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - The Kiwanian, 1978-1979; 182819 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - The Kiwanian, 1979-1980; 182820 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - The Kiwanian, 1980-1981; 182821 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - The Kiwanian, 1981-1982; 182822 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - The Kiwanian, 1982-1983; 182823 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - The Kiwanian, 1983-1984; 182824 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - The Kiwanian, 1984-1985; 182825 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - The Kiwanian, 1985-1986; 182826 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - The Kiwanian, 1986-1987; 182827 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - The Kiwanian, 1987-1988; 182828 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - The Kiwanian, 1988-1989; 182829 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - The Kiwanian, 1989-1990; 182830 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - The Kiwanian, 1990-1991; 182831 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - The Kiwanian, 1991-1992; 182832 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - The Kiwanian, 1992-1993; 182833 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - The Kiwanian, 1993-1994; 182834 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - The Kiwanian, 1994-1995; 182835 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - The Kiwanian, 1995-1996; 182836 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - The Kiwanian, 1996-1997; 182837 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - The Kiwanian, 1997-1998; 182838 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - The Kiwanian, 1998-1999; 182839 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - The Kiwanian, 1999-2000; 182840 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - The Kiwanian, 2000-2001; 182841 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - The Kiwanian, 2001-2002; 182842 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - The Kiwanian, 2002-2003; 182843 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - The Kiwanian, 2003-2004; 182844 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - The Kiwanian, 2004-2005; 182845 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - The Kiwanian, 2005-2006; 182846 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - The Kiwanian, 2006-2007; 182847 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - The Kiwanian, 2007-2008; 182848 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - The Kiwanian, 2008-2009; 182849 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - The Kiwanian, 2009-2010; 182850 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - The Kiwanian, 2010-2011; 182851 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - The Kiwanian, 2011-2012; 182852 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Series VIII: Retired and Deceased Members, 182853
  - Abbot, Sally – Brooks, C.N., 182854 (Box 32)
  - Brower, Paul W. – Cutter, Lewis W., 182855 (Box 33)
  - Dabney, Robert L Jr. – Glenn, Nancy L., 182856 (Box 34)
  - Glist, Louis – Johnson, Elliot A., 182857 (Box 35)
  - Johnson, Gaylord Jr. – Lorehn, Edmond L., 182858 (Box 36)
  - Lovelady, Sim B. – Mitchell, James P., 182859 (Box 37)
  - Mobley, John A. Jr. – Powell, Willis M. Jr., 182860 (Box 38)
  - Pratt, Peter – Short, Wilford Jr., 182861 (Box 39)
  - Sibley, Seth Jr. –Vollus, William G., 182862 (Box 40)
  - Wade, Neal – Zuehl, Matthew J., 182863 (Box 41)
  - Resignations and Deaths, 182864 (Box 41)
- Series IX: Foundation, 182865
  - Foundation Board Materials, 183732
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1979-1980; 182866 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1980-1981, 1981-1982; 182867 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1981-1982; 182868 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1982-1985; 182869 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1985-1987; 182870 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1985-1986, 1986-1987; 182871 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1987-1989; 182872 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1989-1991; 182873 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 1991-1992; 182874 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Steve Schneider, 1991-1993; 182875 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Dennis Fowler, 1992-1993; 182876 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Joe Meyer, 1993-1995; 182877 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Bolivar Andrews, 1995-1997; 182878 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Ed Newhaus, 1997-1999; 182879 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Gerald Giblin, Jr., 1999-2001; 182880 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - International Foundation Annual Report, 1999; 182881 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Gwynne Old, 2001-2003; 182882 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Gabrielle Merrill, 2003-2004; 182883 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Gabrielle Merrill, 2004-2005; 182884 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President Mark Burleson, 2005-2007; 182885 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Board Materials; President David Lucke, 2007-2009; 182886 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Board Materials, 182887 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Minutes, 1966-1972; 182888 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Board Minutes, 1991-1995; 182889 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Foundation Board Minutes, 1996-1997; 182890 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Foundation Founding Documentation, c.1966-1970; 182891 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Letter to the Board re: Finances, 1976; 182892 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Memo: Purpose of Foundation and Instruction to Committee Chair, 182893 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Foundation: Board of Directors Meeting, 2/14/1007; 182894 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Foundation: Officers and Directors, 2002-2003; 182896 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Foundation: Authorization to Withdraw Funds, 2004; 182897 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Foundation: Multi-purpose Certification Forms, 1988-1989; 182898 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Foundation History, 182899 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Kiwanis Foundation By-Laws (old), 182900 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Foundation Gant Requests, 183733
    - Foundation: grant Screening Criteria, 1997; 182901 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Foundation Requests, 1996-1997; 182902 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Grant Application: Miracle Farm, 1997; 182903 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Grant Application: Periwinkle Foundation, 1997-1998; 182904 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Grant Application: Sam Houston Area Council Boy Scouts, 1998; 182905 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Grant Application: Houston Toy Museum, 1997; 182906 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Grant Application: Girl Scouts San Jacinto, 1997-1998; 182908 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Grant Application: Girl Scouts San Jacinto, 1998-1999; 182909 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Grant Application: Volunteer Center of Texas Gulf Coast, 1997-1998; 182910 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Grant Application: Houston Preparatory Academy, , 1997-1998; 182911 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Grant Application: Houston Ear Research Foundation, 1997-1998; 182912 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Grant Application: Center for Hearing and Speech, 1997-1998; 182913 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Grant Application: Center for Hearing and Speech, 1998-1999; 182914 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Grant Application: Neuhaus Education Center, 1997-1998; 182915 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Grant Application: Neuhaus Education Center, 1998-1999; 182916 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Grant Application: Christian Community Service Center, 1997; 182917 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Grant Application: Christian Community Service Center, 1998-1999; 182918 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Grant Application: Boys + Girls Country of Houston, Inc., 1998; 182919 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Grant Application: Camp for All, 1998-1999; 182920 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Grant Application: Camp for All, 1998; 182921 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Grant Application: Hug a Habitat Nature Concerts, 1997-1998; 182922 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Grant Application: Hug a Habitat Nature Concerts, 1999-2000; 182923 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Grant Application: Houston Community Voice Mail, 1998-1999; 182924 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Grant Application: I Have A Dream- Houston, 1998-1999; 182925 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Grant Request INFO, 1998-1999; 182926 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Grant Application: Sam Houston Area Council Boy Scouts, 1998-1999; 182927 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Grant Application: Big Brothers/ Big Sisters of Greater Houston, 1998-1999; 182928 (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - Grant Application: Periwinkle Foundation, 1998-1999; 182929 (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - Grant Application: Volunteer Houston, 1998-1999; 182930 (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Grant Application: Armand Bayou Nature Center, 1998; 182931 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - Grant Application: Amigos de las Americas, 182932 (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - Grant Application: Junior Achievement of South Seat Texas, Inc., 182933 (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Grant Application: Bay Area Habitat for Humanity, 1996-1997; 182934 (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Grant Applications, 2004-2005; 182935 (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Grant Applications, 2005-2006; 182936 (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Grant Application: Depression and BiPolar Support Alliance Greater Houston, 2007-2008; 182937 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Grant Application: Women's Home, 2007-2008; 182938 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Grant Application: Gulf Coast Regional Blood Center, 2007-2008; 182939 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Grant Application: Sire. Inc., 2008-2009; 182940 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Grant Application: Periwinkle Foundation, 2008; 182941 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Grant Application: Girl Scouts of San Jacinto Council, 2007-2008; 182942 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Grant Application: Children at Risk, 2008-2009; 182943 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Grant Application: I Have A Dream Houston, 2008-2009; 182944 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Grant Application: Archway Academy, 2007; 182945 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Grant Application: Aldine Youth, Inc., 2007-2008; 182946 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Grant Application: Center for Hearing and Speech, 2007-2008; 182947 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Grant Application: Christian Community Service Center, 2008; 182948 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Grant Application: Houston Area Women's Center, 2006-2007; 182950 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Grant Application: Casa De Esperanza, 2007-2008; 182951 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Grant Application: Houston Area Research Center Foundation, 2007-2008; 182952 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Grant Application: Young Life, 2007-2008; 182953 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Grant Application: Center For hearing and Speech, 2008; 182954 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Grant Application: Neuhaus Education Center, 2007-2008; 182955 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Grant Application: Boys and Girls Country, 2008; 182956 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Grant Application: Carolina Creek Christian Camp, 2008; 182957 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Grant Application: Children at Risk, 2010; 182958 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Grant Application: Young Life, 2010-2011; 182959 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Grant Application: Child Builders, 2010-2011; 182960 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Grant Application: Weather Researcher Center, Inc., 2010-2011; 182961 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Grant Application: Houston Ear Research Foundation, 2010-2011; 182962 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Grant Application: Nehemiah Center, Inc., 2010-2011; 182963 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Grant Application: Harris Foundation, 2010-2011; 182964 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Grant Application: Sire, 2011; 182965 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Grant Application: Depression and Bipolar Support Alliance- Great Houston, 2010-2011; 182966 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Grant Application: Boys and Girls Country, 2011; 182967 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Grant Application: Houston Achievement Place, 2011; 182968 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Grant Application: Escape Family Resource Center, 2010-2011; 182969 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Grant Application: Child Advocates, Inc., 2011; 182970 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Grant Application: Amigos de las Americas, 2011-2012; 182971 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Grant Application: Girl Scouts of San Jacinto Council, 2011; 182972 (Box 44, Folder 35)